{
    "subject": "resource/Nina's_Heavenly_Delights",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Laura_Fraser",
    "human_readable": "Nina's Heavenly Delights stars Laura Fraser.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8432152271270752,
            "question": "Who stars in the show Nina's Heavenly Delights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.74574875831604,
            "question": "Is Nina's Heavenly Delights a comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6697074174880981,
            "question": "Is Laura Fraser an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6350497007369995,
            "question": "What other roles has Laura Fraser played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6190345883369446,
            "question": "What genre is Nina's Heavenly Delights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6039767265319824,
            "question": "What is the name of the show that features Laura Fraser?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5686225295066833,
            "question": "What is the plot of Nina's Heavenly Delights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.558628261089325,
            "question": "Where can I watch Nina's Heavenly Delights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5492329001426697,
            "question": "Are there any awards associated with Nina's Heavenly Delights?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4792202115058899,
            "question": "Is Laura Fraser a Scottish actress?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nina's Heavenly Delights stars Laura Fraser.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3508_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any awards associated with Nina's Heavenly Delights?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3508_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch Nina's Heavenly Delights?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3508_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of Nina's Heavenly Delights?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3508_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3508_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3508_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3508_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3508_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3508_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3508_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3508_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3508_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3508_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3508_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"Starring: Laura Fraser, Shelley Conn, Art Malik, Ronny Jhutti, Veena Sood\" and further detail about her role in the film. This confirms that Laura Fraser is one of the stars of \"Nina's Heavenly Delights\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}